Curriculum Vitae

Name: Aðalsteinn Ari Gunnarsson

Date of birth: January 17th, 2002

Phone: +354 896 6002

Email: aarigunn0717@gmail.com



ABOUT ME

My name is Aŏalsteinn Ari Gunnarsson, I'm 22 years old. I am in the process of completing my third year in the Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering at the University of Iceland. I'm a hardworking and extremely driven individual who excels both independently and within collaborative group settings. Outside of my academic commitments, I engage in various interests, including football, golf, and weightlifting.

EDUCATION

University of Iceland

2021-present

Bachelor of Science, Mechanical Engineering.

- First class distinction.
- Currently in my final year

Commercial College of Iceland

2018-2021

Matriculation in nature science and physics.

- GPA 9.2 out of 10
- Received a certification for an outstanding performance in mathematics from the Icelandic Mathematical Society.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Brautarholt Golf Club

2018-2023

- Worked in the construction of the golf course.
- Worked in the installation and planning of automated, electric mowers.

Origo 2023-2023

- Worked as a service representative for a computer workshop.
- Fixed computers.

University of Iceland

2023-Present

- Teacher assistant in practical physics.
- Teacher assistant in computer programming.
- Taught classes, and graded assignments.

SKILLS

- Microsoft programs
- Python
- Matlab
- Java

Autocad

C++

- Inventor
- Ansys

- Public speaking
- Interpersonal skills
- Resilience
- Attention to detail

LANGUAGES

English C1 (advanced) TOEFL score: 103 Native speaker

Icelandic

Danish

Matriculation examination

Matriculation Spanish examination

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

2023-Present **Schools paper**

- Writing articles.
- Providing funding for the student community.

Team Spark 2023-Present

- Formula Student team.
- In the chassis team.
- Worked with a lot of metal and carbon fiber.